TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
해 보자!
Letz do diz!
좋아, 칸타로스, 가라!
Yez, go attack, Cantaros!
아, 내가 먼저 보고 있었잖아!
Hey, I was sitting here first!
시꺼. 난 이거 보고 싶으니까.
Shaddup. I wanna watch this.
뭐야. 오빠 싫어. 아까부터 계속 하나하나 잡아물고.
I hate you when you're like that. You're getting in my way all the time!
싫었으니 딱 잘 됐네. 흥!
You hate me, and I like that. Good enough!
베이어니트하고 있었던 때 오빠가 지금보다 훨씬 나았어!
You were way better when you were with Bayonet!
내 앞에서 베이어니트 이야기하지 말랬지!
I told you not to talk about Bayonet in front of me!
원하는 거나 봐!
Just watch what you want!
됐다! 조금만 더!
Almost there!
형 바보.
Oh, brother...
베이어니트...
Bayonet...
일어나라! 긴카이
Stand Up! Ginkai
(en: Once a Medafighter - Part I)
원하는 만큼 가져가도 돼.
You may take as much as you want.
이 정도 있으면 충분해. 헤.
This is more than enough. Heh.
데스 메다로트 사에서 메일이 도착했습니다.
Death Medarot Company sent you an e-mail.
열어.
Open.
좋아.
That's great.
뭐야?
What's up?
버그나서 폭주했던 블로소메일이 곧 완성된대.
Blossomail's bugs have been fixed and is almost ready to be released.
그 블로소메일?
You mean that Blossomail?
자유롭게 쓸 수 있게 된 거야?
Will it follow your orders properly, then?
그래. 블로소메일이라면 메타비 따위는 간단히 쓰러뜨릴 수 있을 거야.
Yes. Blossomail should be able to knock Metabee down easily.
엑스사이즈는 어쩌고?
What about Excise?
블로소메일이 손에 들어오면 더는 볼 일 없어.
When Blossomail's in my hands, I have no business with it anymore.
보, 볼 일 없다고? 함께 싸워 왔는데 아무 느낌도 안 드는 거야?
N- no business!? Aren't you feeling any sentiment towards him despite all the fights you've done together?
딱히.
Not really.
그보다, 엑스사이즈한테 최후로 날뛸 기회를 줄 생각인데, 따라올래?
Anyway, I'm going to let Excise have its last rage. Will you join me?
어... 그래.
Er... sure.
어! 기습이라니 너무하잖아!
Hey! Surprise attack is not fair!
게임은 이제부터야.
The game didn't even begun.
어?
What?
긴카이.
Ginkai.
유니트리스! 놈을 흔들어 일으켜 연속 펀치!
Unitrix! Wake him up and do consecutive punches!
무슨!
No way!
그만해!
Stop it!
메다로트치고 튼튼하기만 해서 거 잘 안 부서지는구먼.
That Medarot is pretty durable, I see. It's still holding, eh.
부탁이야! 미니 부수지 마!
Please! Don't destory Mini!
제발! 미니는 내 보물이야!
I'm begging you! Mini is my treasure!
다들 조용히 있지만 말고 뭐라고 좀 해 줘. 부탁이니까 친구해 줘.
Don't just stand there silently; say something! Please let me be your friend!
나 혼자서 로보틀은 못 한단 말야.
I can't do Robattles by myself.
넌 너무 강하잖아.
You're too good at it.
너무 강해서 너하고 로보틀해도 재미 없어.
It's no fun Robattling with you since you're too good.
무슨!
No way!
잠깐! 잠깐만!
Wait! Don't go!
너같이 약한 놈은 정말 싫단 말이지!
I hate weaklings just like you!
유니트리스! 끝장내라!
Unitrix! Finish him!
미니!
Mini!
꽤나 열심히 했나 보네. 꽤 재밌었나 봐, 긴카이.
You look like you had fun, Ginkai.
그럼, 다음으로 가자.
Let's try someone else, shall we?
원망할 거라면 네가 못하는 걸 원망해라.
If you're going to blame, then blame your own weakness.
뭐야. 오빠 싫어. 아까부터 계속 하나하나 잡아물고.
I hate you when you're like that. You're getting in my way all the time!
베이어니트하고 있었던 때 오빠가 지금보다 훨씬 나았어!
You were way better when you were with Bayonet!
너한테 말해봤자 못 알아듣긴 하겠지만, 요즘은 쌈질에서 이겨도 하나도 재미 없고 말야.
You probably can't understand this, but anyway, there's no fun in winning battles recently.
어?
Huh?
알았으니까 이제 그만해!
I get it! You can stop now!
헤헤, 젠틀하트, 더 아프게 해 줘라!
Heh, Gentleheart, hurt him more!
카파로드!
Kapparoad!
젠틀하트, 아예 깔아뭉개 버려!
Gentleheart, trample him!
하지 마!
Don't do it!
멈춰라!
Stop right there!
뭐야, 넌?
What's your business?
약하다고 괴롭하면 안된다고 말했다!
Again, I told you that you may not bully someone for being weak!
건방지긴! 젠틀하트, 저 놈을 쓰러뜨려!
Trying to get on my nerves? Gentleheart, take them down for good!
그려.
Yeah, sure.
베이어니트, 라이플로 팔을 쏘아!
Bayonet, aim at his arms and fire!
물론!
Roger!
가까이 가서 양팔에 미사일 발사!
Approach and shoot missiles towards both arms!
맡겨두셔!
Leave it to me!
양팔 파트, 기능 정지.
Both arm parts stopped functioning.
이제 틀렸어! 해머를 쓸 수 없어!
It's no good! Hammers are out of option!
젠장, 시합 포기다! 젠틀하트!
Dammit, we're forfeiting this match! Gentleheart!
그려.
Yeah, sure.
잘 했어, 베이어니트!
Good job, Bayonet!
카파로드!
Kapparoad!
괜찮아?
Are you alright?
긴카이, 네가 너무 잘한다고 멀리했던거 미안.
Ginkai, I'm sorry for leaving you out for being too strong.
다 괜찮아.
It's forgiven.
-대단해, 긴카이!
-어떻게 해야 로보틀에서 이길 수 있어? 알려 줘!
-You're awesome, Ginkai!
-What do you do to win a Robattle? Tell us!
뭐, 좋아! 일단 상대의 약점을 알아내는 거야.
No problem! First, start with finding out your opponent's weaknesses.
젠틀하트는 움직임이 느리지만 장갑은 두꺼워. 그래서 한방에 무기인 팔을 공격하는 거야.
Gentleheart is slow, but his armors are thick. That makes attacking his weapons - his arms - directly the best option.
팔 기능을 정지시키기만 하면 끝난 거랑 마찬가지!
If you manage to make his arms stop functioning, then you practically win!
뭐, 나하고 베이어니트의 조합이 승리의 열쇠이긴 하지만 말야!
Well, even better, the combination of Bayonet and me is the key to victory!
-아, 그런 거야?
-대단해!     -멋져!
-Oh, is that so?
-That's awesome!       -Cool!
그 때가 더 두근두근거리고 매일이 재미있었고.
Those days were more exciting and enjoyable without a day missing.
잇키! 메타비!
Ikki! Metabee!
아리카!
Arika!
뭔 일이야?
What's up?
이번 일요일에 메다로트 사 주최 로보틀 대회가 열린대!
There's a Robattle competition held by Medarot Company upcoming this sunday!
어, 정말이냐?
Heh, you sure!?
응, 우승자에게는 아크비틀 대시하고 티렐비틀이 상품이래!
Yeah! Even more interesting is Arcbeetle Dash and Tyrelbeetle are for the winner!
그때 그 신형 말야?
Those new types before?
있잖아, 잇키, 상품은 필요 없어도, 오랜만에 로보틀에서 크게 날뛰어 보는 거 어때!?
Hey, Ikki, not that we need those prizes, but why not join the Robattles and show who's boss!?
좋아!
Great idea!
-좋아! 등록하러 가자!
-Alright! Let's go register!
잠깐!
Wait for me!
로보틀 대회라?
Robattle competition, eh?
로보틀 대회 당일
Robattle Competition Day
야, 유즈루!
Hey, Yuzuru!
어, 다들 안녕하세요.
Hey, good morning.
너희도 로보틀 대회에 참가할 거야?
Are you guys joining Robattle competition too?
아, 아니, 우린 그냥 산책하러 나왔어요.
Er, no, we're just out for a walk.
그럼 우리하고 같이 참가하러 가자!
Then, let's go register together!
우, 우린 괜찮아요.
W- we're fine without that.
뭔 소리야! 로보틀은 메다로터와 메다로트의 우정을 더욱 깊게 할 수 있는 최고의 기회야! 가자, 가!
What are you saying? Robattles are the best chances to deepen the friendship between Medarot and Medarotter! Let's go!
돈도그도 나가고 싶지? 가자, 자, 자!
You wanna join too, Dondogu, right? Let's go, go!
역시 남자얘들이네.
Boys will be boys.
어! 스크류즈!
Look! Screws!
어!
Look!
설마 니들도 참가할 거냐!?
Are you guys gonna join too!?
-당연.
-Of course.
두목, 이제 우승을 틀렸네요!
Boss, you already lost!
싸우기 전부터 무기력하게!
I didn't even fight yet, you wimp!
죄, 죄송합니다!
I- I'm sorry!
헤헤, 정직한 의견이라고 생각하는데 말이지.
Heh, I think he was just being very straight.
닥쳐닥쳐닥쳐! 오늘 대회는 내가 우승하고 아크비틀 대시하고 티렐비틀을 가져갈 거야!
Shut up, shut up, shut up! I'm winning today's competition and I'm taking Arcbeetle Dash and Tyrelbeetle!
그럴 수는 있냐? 우리 세계 대회 준우승 콤비를 상대로 될 거라고 생각하냐?
Can you? Do you really think you're defeating us, the almost-winners of the world championship!?
승부는 그때그때의 운이야!
Victories require luck!
카가미야마, 말 잘 했다!
Kagamiyama, well said!
운만으로 이길 거라고 생각하다니 싱겁군! 실력이 먼저지!
Do you really think that luck is all you need? Your capabilities come first!
그것도 일리 있네.
Makes sense.
누구 편이냐!
Whose side are you on!?
죄, 죄송합니다!
I- I'm sorry.
어쨌든 결승전에서 기다릴 테니까 잇키, 메타비! 너희돌 살아남아서 와라.
Anyway, I'll be waiting at the final match! Ikki and Metabee, do not drop out before then.
두목 멋져요!
Boss, you're so cool!
저런 자신감은 대체 어디서 나오는 거야?
Where does she get all the confidence?
그러게 말야.
Totally agreed.
저런저런.
Oh my.
메다로트 사 주최 음양 마을 로보틀 대회
Ginjo Town Robattle Competition
Sponsored by Medarot Company
지금부터 오늘의 로보틀 대회 규칙을 메다로트 박사님이 설명해 주시겠습니다!
Medarot Professor will explain today's Robattle competition rules!
1 시합의 시합 시간은 3분. 승패는 기능 정지시킨 쪽이 이기는 것으로 한다.
One match will take 3 minutes. Whoever keeps functioning to the last will be the winner.
시간 내 결과가 안 나면 대미지의 비율로 결정한다.
If the match isn't set until the time limit, the victory will be decided by the ratio of damage dealt.
대미지 포인트는 저기에 그대로 표시되고 또한 남은 시간도 표시됩니다.
Both damage points and remaining time are displayed there.
링 아웃의 경우에는 카운트다운으로 패배로 한다.
In case one goes out of the ring, one will lose after a countdown.
로보틀 정신을 잊지 말고 열심히 해 주길 바란다. 이상!
Please don't forget the Robattle spirits and do your best. That's all!
우승하면 상품은 유즈루한테 주자!
If we win, let's give the prize to Yuzuru!
괜찮네!
Good idea!
그럼 1회전, A 블록의 제 1 시합을 개시합니다!
The first match of the group A is about to begin!
유즈루 선수와 돈도그!
Yuzuru and Dondogu!
유즈루 군! 힘내!
Yuzuru! Do your best!
-힘내, 유즈루!
-돈도그!
-Make it, Yuzuru!
-Dondogu!
VS. 마스크드 Q 선수와 유니트리스!
VS. Masked Q and Unitrix!
마스크드 Q!
Masked Q!
긴카이! 왜 니가 나왔냐!?
Ginkai! Why are you even here!?
어, 어떻게 안 거야!?
H- how did you figured it out!?
너 그것도 변장이라고 한 거냐?
Are you saying that that's your disguise?
뭐, 얼굴 보면 딱 안될 거라고 나오네.
Your face tells everything!
너 시끄러! 조금 놀고 싶어졌을 뿐이다!
Shut up, you! I'm here to play, and that's all!
우승은 나와 유니트리스가 가져가겠어!
Unitrix and I will take the victory!
이랴.
Here I go...
규칙이 있는 로보틀에서 네가 이길 리가 없잖아!
You're not winning a Robattle where rules are!
흥, 어디 한번 보시라.
Hmph. You'll see.
Medarot Damashii - Subtitles by Subdiver
로보틀 파이트!
Robattle fight!
돈도그, 기능 정지, 기능 정지.
Dondogu stopped functioning.
기능 정지. 유니트리스 승리.
Function stopped. Unitrix wins.
엄청 약하네...
Super weak...
키쿠히메와 페퍼캣 VS. 이와노이와 블루즈독 전을 시작합니다!
We'll begin the match between Kikuhime and Peppercat VS. Iwanoi and Bluesdog shortly!
이와노이, 알지?
Iwanoi, you know what to do.
로보틀 파이트!
Robattle fight!
페퍼캣! 라이트 블로다!
Peppercat! Use Light Blow!
어, 엄청 강해!
S- super strong!
완전 내가 상대할 상대가
No way I'm
아니야!
winning!
시, 시합 포기!
M- match forfeited!
페퍼캣의 승리!
Peppercat wins!
좋아! 페퍼캣! 곧 티렐비틀과 아크대시가 네 아우가 될 거야!
Alright! Peppercat, you'll have Tyrelbeetle and Arcdash as your younger brothers!
꼬라지하고는...
What an act.
보는 내가 다 부끄럽다.
I'm embarassed.
속 다 보이네.
I just can't.
티피, 기능 정지. 메타비 승리!
Teepee stopped functioning. Metabee wins!
-잘 한다, 메타비!
-별 거 아냐!
-Good job, Metabee!
-It was nothing!
-예이!
-Yeah!
계속해서 2회전을 시작합니다.
We'll begin the second set of matches!
마스크드 Q 선수의 유니트리스 VS. 카가미야마 선수의 키스터틀!
Masked Q's Unitrix versus Kagamiyama's Kiethturtle!
카가미야마, 마스크드 Q를 쓰러트리면 A블록에서 결승에 진출하는 건 내가 돼. 꼭 부탁한다.
Kagamiyama, if you manage to take Masked Q down, I'll be the finalist from the group A. Do all you can.
그 데스 메다로트의 메다로터가 누군진 모르지만 맡겨만 주세요!
I have no idea who's that Medarotter using Death Medarot, but leave it to me!
부탁한다!
I'm counting on you!
로보틀 파이트!
Robattle fight!
한번에 어깨를 붙여! 유니트리스, 레클리스 모드!
Get your shoulders to him! Unitrix, Reckless Mode!
끝장내라, 유니트리스!
Finish him, Unitrix!
대, 대미지 포인트가...
M- my damage points...
키스터틀...
Kiethturtle...
유니트리스 승리!
Unitrix wins!
-꽤 하네.
-우리도 질 순 없지!
-He's pretty good.
-We're not losing here!
-메타비!
-잇키!
-Metabee!
-Ikki!
기능 정지. 유니트리스 승리.
Function ceased. Unitrix wins!
무, 무슨!
N- no way!
-두목! 정신 차려요!
-Boss! Get a grip!
어디서 굴러먹던 개뼈다귀인지도 모르는 마스크드 Q에게 지다니!
How can I lose to nobody-from-heaven-or-hell-knows-who!?
좋아, 결승 진출이다!
Alright, we're joining the final match!
형!
Hey!
형 강하네요!
Hey, you're strong!
사인해 주세요!
Can you make an autograph for me?
사, 사인?
A- autograph?
부탁해요!
Please do so!
어, 그래.
Well, why not.
유니트리스 & 마스크드 Q
Unitrix & Masked Q
이걸로 되지?
I hope this is enough.
형 결승전에서도 이겨요!
You gotta win the final match!
어, 맡겨둬!
Sure, leave it to me!
오호라, 긴카이 놈, 꽤나 여유롭네?
Ginkai's pretty relaxed!
메타비는 어때?
How's Metabee doing?
나에 씨, 이 시합에서 이기면 결승 진출이에요!
Ms. Nae, they're joining the final match if they win this match!
어택 티라노, 기능 정지. 메타비 승리!
Attack Tyrano stopped functioning. Metabee wins!
-해냈어!
-좋았어, 메타비!
-I did it!
-Well done, Metabee!
나이스 파이트!
Nice fight!
자, 드디어 오늘의 대회의 결승전입니다!
Now, it's finally time for today's final match!
우승자에게는 메다로트 사의 신형 메다로트, 아크비틀 대시 그리고 티렐비틀이 상품으로 주어집니다!
The winner will be awarded with the Medarots of new type from Medarot Company: Arcbeetle Dash and Tyrelbeetle!
결승전은 5분. 그래도 승패가 안 나면 날 때까지 무제한으로 연장전에 돌입합니다!
The final match will take 5 minutes. If there is no winner yet, then we'll allow unlimited extension of the match!
그럼 지금부터 결승전을 시작합니다!
Now, we'll begin the final match!
마스크드 Q 선수와 유니트리스!
Masked Q and Unitrix!
Q!
유니트리스 파이트!
Unitrix, fight!
잇키 선수와 메타비!
Ikki and Metabee!
메타비! 꼭 우승해!
Metabee! You'll win!
어? 마스크드 Q 선수, 마스크를 벗습니다!
Look! Masked Q is taking off his mask!
쟤 긴카이였어!
Was he Ginkai!?
저 뻔하디 뻔한 걸 이제야 알아차리다니.
How couldn't they figure that out until now?
저것들은 내가 가져가겠다!
I'll be taking those!
우리한테 이기고나 나서 할 소리다!
You'll have to get through us first!
마스크드 Q, 즉, 긴카이 선수 대 잇키 선수, 누가 이길 것인가!
Masked Q or Ginkai versus Ikki - who will win!?
로보틀 파이트!
Robattle fight!
이게 뭔 괴력이야, 이게!
What kind of raw strength is this!?
상관 없어, 메타비! 레클리스 모드!
Ignore that, Metabee! Reckless Mode!
이랴!
Here I go!
우리도 레클리스 모드다! 유니트리스!
Reckless mode for us, too! Unitrix!
어디 보자!
We'll see!
꽤 하잖아!?
He's pretty good!
규칙을 지키면서 여기까지 올 거라고는 생각도 못 했어!
I never thought he would make his way up to here under the rules!
유니트리스의 진짜 힘은 이 정도가 아니야! 그라피티 모드, 유니트리스!
Unitrix can do much more than this! To Graffiti Mode, Unitrix!
우리도다! 메타비, 그라피티 모드다!
We'll do that too! Metabee, to Graffiti Mode!
좋아!
Alright!
유니트리스가 훨씬 강하니까 조심해!
Unitrix is far stronger, so be careful!
기회야, 메타비! 메다스플레이어!
A chance, Metabee! Medasplayer!
좋아!
Got it!
어, 어라?
H- huh?
메타비! 위야!
Metabee! Up!
메다로즈야, 유니트리스!
Use Medarose, Unitrix!
정신 차려, 메타비! 노멀 모드!
Get up, Metabee! Normal Mode!
젠장!
Damn you!
유니트리스, 메다로즈 준비!
Unitrix, prepare Medarose!
힘내, 메타비!
Stay focused, Metabee!
유니트리스, 끝장이다!
Unitrix, finish him!
중지! 시간 초과!
Stop! Time over!
칫.
Hmph.
정식 로보틀이군. 재밌네.
So that was an official Robattle. Pretty fun.
완전 위험했다...
That was so close...
저 긴카이가 공격을 멈췄어.
Ginkai actually stopped attacking.
규칙을 지키고 있어.
He's abiding by the rules.
1분 휴식 이후 연장선을 개시합니다.
We'll have a break for a minute, and begin the extended match.
메타비! 괜찮아, 메타비?
Metabee! Are you alright, Metabee?
응, 어.
Er, yeah.
브, 블로소메일!
B- Blossomail!
블로소메일!
Blossomail!
긴카이.
Ginkai.
코쿠류!
Kokuryu!
메타비를 때려눕힐 기회인데 뭘 놀고 있어?
It's your chance to smash Metabee up, so why are you slacking?
이, 이건 그냥 쌈질이 아냐. 로보틀이야.
T- this isn't just a plain quarreling! It's a Robattle!
시시하긴. 네가 안 할 거라면, 내가 할게.
How boring. If you aren't going to do so, then I will.
뭐, 뭐야!?
W- what's that!?
갑자기 난입해서는 이게 뭔 짓이야!
Intrusion is already bad, and now what!?
블로소메일, 한번에 메타비를 끝장내! 레클리스 모드!
Blossomail, deal with Metabee at once! Reckless Mode!
그만둬, 코쿠류! 이건 나하고 텐료 잇키의 정식 로보틀이야!
Stop it, Kokuryu! This is an official Robattle between Tenryo Ikki and me!
관계 없어. 해, 블로소메일!
So what? Do it, Blossomail!
그, 그만해!
S- stop that!
제기랄!
Damn!
그만해, 코쿠류!
Stop that, Kokuryu!
믿을 수가 없군. 저게 그 소문의 코쿠류인가.
I can't believe this. He's that Kokuryu?
누구도 날 막지 못할 거야. 블로소메일, 그라피티 모드.
Nobody shall stop me. Blossomail, to Graffiti Mode.
형!
Ginkai!
막아 줘! 메타비를 구해줘!
Please stop him! Please save Metabee!
형! 빨리!
Ginkai! Hurry!
뭐야. 오빠 싫어. 아까부터 계속 하나하나 잡아물고.
I hate you when you're like that. You're getting in my way all the time!
베이어니트하고 있었던 때 오빠가 지금보다 훨씬 나았어!
You were way better when you were with Bayonet!
메타비!
Metabee!
메타비, 대미지 포인트 100. 기능 정지, 기능 정지.
Metabee, 100 damage points. Function ceased. Function ceased.
메타비!
Metabee!
좋아, 블로소메일, 메달을 부수어버려.
Good, Blossomail. Now smash the medal.
그만해!
Stop!
뭔 짓이야, 긴카이.
What was that for, Ginkai?
방해하지 말아 줘, 코쿠류. 난 네 도움 없이도 메타비를 이겼어.
Please don't interfere, Kokuryu. I defeated Metabee without your help.
여긴 로보틀 대회야. 그냥 쌈질하는 곳이 아니야!
This is a Robattle competition. We're not quarreling here!
그러니까 이 이상 날뛰는 건 하지 말아 줘!
So I'll ask you not to go wild anymore!
부탁이야! 이렇게!
Please! I'm asking you!
뭔 소리야, 긴카이.
What are you talking about, Ginkai?
부탁이야, 코쿠류! 오늘은 여기서 물러나 줘!
Please, Kokuryu! Please go back for today!
이해해 줘. 우리 친구잖아?
Please understand. Aren't we friends?
그렇지. 친구니까 내 손발이 되어 명령대로 해야지.
Right. Since we're friends, you're supposed to do exactly as I tell you.
뭐라고? 그런 건 친구가 아니야!
What did you say!? That is not what friend is about!
너한테 뭐든지 다 주고 있잖아. 내가 말하는 대로 안 하면 더는 새 파트나 탄약이나 그런 거 안 줄 건데, 괜찮아?
I'm giving you whatever you want. If you don't do as I say, then you're not getting new parts or ammo. Is that fine?
그, 그건...
Well, that's...
그럼 비켜.
Then, get out of my way.
형!
Ginkai!
자, 블로소메일, 메타비 메달.
Now, Blossomail, take Metabee's medal.
그만두라 했겠다! 유니트리스, 가라!
I told you to stop! Unitrix, go!
긴카이.
Ginkai.
내 명령을 거역했네. 용서하지 않을 거야, 긴카이.
You defied me. I'm not going to forgive you, Ginkai.
긴카이.
Ginkai.
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
코쿠류하고 결별한 긴카이.
Ginkai parted with Kokuryu.
유니트리스와도 떨어진 후, 최신형 메다로트 아크대시를 손에 넣는다.
After also parting with Unitrix, he gets a new type Medarot: Arcdash.
배신자 긴카이를 코쿠류가 용서할 리가 없다.
There's no way Kokuryu's forgiving Ginkai the traitor.
최강의 데스 메다로트, 블로소메일이 긴카이의 아크대시에게 다가온다.
The strongest Death Medarot, Blossomail, is approaching towards Ginkai's Arcdash.
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 코쿠류의 역습
Next time on Medarot Damashii! Kokuryu's Revenge
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!